(
"ai_sub_version": "1.12.0",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 3,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"encoder": "h264_qsv"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
#桃鈴ねね誕生日ライブ2026 ～Liminal～
#MomosuzuNeneBirthdayLive2026 ~Liminal~
いっせーので鳴り響いた
At the count of three, it rang out
スタートの合図
The signal to start
かくれんぼ
作詞：TKT 作曲：EREN
Hide and Seek
Lyrics: TKT, Composition: EREN
謎と線で結んだ世界
A world connected by riddles and lines
彩りつけていく ここから
I'll start coloring it in from here
物心がつく頃
By the time I was old enough to know
既にここにあった僕
I was already here
...じゃない誰かの記憶は
...memories of someone who isn't me
夕陽と共に蘇る
Resurrect with the setting sun
古ぼけた絵本を取り出して
Taking out a worn-out picture book
落書きの中に一つの
I found a single answer
答えを見つけた
Within the scribbles
自分の価値に目を疑って
Doubting my own worth
どこまでだって落ちていけるの
How far down can I fall?
どこか遠くに消えてしまいたい
I want to disappear somewhere far away
こんな世界じゃ僕は要らない
In a world like this, I'm not needed
カウントダウンは始まっているよ
The countdown has already begun
いっせーのーで声を上げて
One, two, raise your voice
聞こえてくるんだ
I can hear it coming
自分の影の長さに気づくの
Noticing the length of my own shadow
そんな時間だ
It's that time of day
愛想が顔を出した
A smile showed its face
届きそうで手を伸ばした
Reaching out as if I could touch it
次は僕に付いてきなよ
Next time, come along with me
暗闇でも
Even through the darkness
もう一回
One more time
まだだよ
Not yet
幕は上がり出した
The curtain has begun to rise
もう一回
One more time
まだだよ
Not yet
色づいていく
Starting to gain color
ここから
From here on
10年後の僕らは
Ten years from now, we'll be...
すれ違いばかりで
Always passing each other by
喧騒に思いを馳せては
Thinking back on the hustle and bustle
戻れないそう思い込んだ
Convinced we could never go back
くたびれた心に追い打ちを
Adding insult to a worn-out heart
あの頃と変わらない夕陽も
Even the sunset, unchanged from back then
何とも思わない
Means nothing to me anymore
自分を信じ歩いて行ければ
If I could believe in myself and walk on
どこまでだって登れるのにな
I could have climbed anywhere
立ち止まるその空白に
In that blank space where I stopped
大切なもの見落としている
I'm overlooking something precious
見つけられないと泣き喚く君へ
To you, who's wailing that you can't find it
いっせーのーで声を上げて
One, two, raise your voice
聞こえてくるんだ
I can hear it coming
自分の影の長さに気づくの
Noticing the length of my own shadow
そんな時間だ
It's that time of day
一生で駆け抜ける君
You, who runs through a whole lifetime
くっ付いていただけの僕でも
Even if I was just clinging to you
君の前を歩けるかな
I wonder if I can walk ahead of you
拙い僕でも
Clumsy as I am
玉手箱は
The treasure chest
埃を
Covered in dust
被ったまま失くした
I lost it while it was still covered
鍵はずっと君の
The key was always
ポケットの中にあった
In your pocket all along
散らばってた全てが
Everything that was scattered
今一つに重なる
Is overlapping into one now
手を取り始めよう
Let's take each other's hands and start
僕たちの物語
Our story
玉手箱は
The treasure chest
いらないと
I don't need it
被ったまま失くした
I lost it while it was still covered
鍵はずっと君の
The key was always
ポケットの中にあった
In your pocket all along
散らばってた全てが
Everything that was scattered
愛おしくて
Is so precious
今一つに重なる
And is overlapping into one now
掛け声はいつも
The shout is always...
いっせーのーで
One, two...
声を上げて
...raise your voice
いっせーのーで声を上げて
One, two, raise your voice
聞こえてくるんだ
I can hear it coming
自分の影の長さに気づくの
Noticing the length of my own shadow
そんな時間だ
It's that time of day
愛想が顔を出した
A smile showed its face
届きそうで手を伸ばした
Reaching out as if I could touch it
次は僕に付いてきなよ
Next time, come along with me
暗闇でも
Even through the darkness
もう一回
One more time
まだだよ
Not yet
泣き出した歌声で
With a voice that's started to cry
もう一回
One more time
まだだよ
Not yet
笑う君が見えた
I saw you smiling
もう一回
One more time
まだだよ
Not yet
幕は上がり出した
The curtain has begun to rise
もう一回
One more time
もういいよ
It's enough now
色づいていく
Starting to gain color
ここから
From here on
鉛の空 重く垂れ込め
Lead-colored sky hangs heavy
真白に澱んだ 太陽が砕けて
The pure white, stagnant sun shatters
耳鳴りを 尖らせる
Sharpening the ringing in my ears
ひゅるりひゅるり 低空飛行
Whirling, whirling, flying low
蜂の字なぞって ビルの谷を駆ける
Tracing a figure-eight, running through the valleys of buildings
もうじきに 夕立が来る
Soon, an evening shower will come
曇天の道を 傘を忘れて
On a cloudy road, forgetting my umbrella
歩く彼女は 雨に怯えてる
She walks, afraid of the rain
ので 僕も 弱虫ぶら下げて
So I too, hanging my cowardice
空を仰ぐ
Look up at the sky
あちらこちら あんよは上手
Here and there, walking so well
珈琲屋に寄って 一休み決めたら
Stopping by a coffee shop, once I decide to take a break
帰れない 帰らない
I can't go back, I won't go back
曇天の道を ぶらりぶらぶら
On a cloudy road, wandering aimlessly
歩く二人は 足軽のごとく
The two walking like foot soldiers
危険好きの 誰かのふりをする
Pretending to be someone who loves danger
初心者共
Beginners
曇天の道を 傘を忘れて
On a cloudy road, forgetting my umbrella
歩く彼女は 雨に怯えてる
She walks, afraid of the rain
ので 僕も 弱虫ぶら下げて
So I too, hanging my cowardice
空を仰ぐ
Look up at the sky
放っておいて育つもの
Things that grow if you leave them alone
何だ 何だろ?
What is it? I wonder what it is?
One more chance! One more chance!
Never never give up!
Perfect-area complete!
運営さんなんか放送エコーが切れてるかもとのことで確認お願いします
Staff, it seems the broadcast echo might be cut off, so please check.
出会いましては簡単すぎよ
Meeting you was too easy
最初に決めた答えはひとつ
The answer I first decided on was one
ときめきました合格しますか?
I felt a spark, will I pass?
恋も勝負もあわてない
Don't rush love or a match
コツコツコツと徹夜にため息
Step by step, sighing through all-nighters
私の中に天才ドリマー
There's a genius dreamer inside me
思うこと皆叶えばいいな
I wish everything I thought of would come true
人の世界は気にしない
I don't care about other people's worlds
Perfect-area complete!
絶対ここで待ってるんだ
I'm definitely waiting here
Perfect-area 望む声が
Perfect-area, the voices wishing for it
聞こえるよ
I can hear them
Ai-ai-ya!
ほら止まらない すれ違い
Look, it won't stop, passing each other
私が壮大天下なら
If I ruled the grand world
友達かい?
Are we friends?
友達です!
We are friends!
悲しきレッテルのやり直し
Redoing the sad labels
書き直し
Rewriting
本気でワン・チャンス!
Seriously one chance!
今より素敵な未来があるのに
Even though there's a more wonderful future than now
今より素敵に My life, my life, my life!
More wonderful than now, my life, my life, my life!
あざーす！みんなもありがとう！
Thanks! Thank you everyone too!
続きましてはお月様にも
Next, even to the moon
お星様にも
And to the stars
科学的にはどうにもならず
Scientifically nothing can be done
輝きました明日を夢見て
It shined, dreaming of tomorrow
恋で我慢を
Patience through love
学んだね
I've learned
ムクムクムクと広がる雨雲
Puffy rain clouds spreading
私を濡らす瞬間スコール
A sudden squall soaking me
悩みごとほら流れたみたい
Look, it seems my worries washed away
泣き言なんて忘れよう
Let's forget about complaints
Fascination conversation
感動したいもっとずっと
I want to be moved more and forever
イヤイヤ　ワー！
No, no, wa-!
さりげなく聞いてみた
I casually tried asking
私は勉強速くて
I'm a fast learner
可能性ありますか
Is there a possibility?
試験は何点か　イェーイ！
What's my test score? Yay!
誰だって　君だって
Anyone, even you
間に合うギリ間に合っちょ
Can make it, just barely make it
これから始まる季節にご挨拶
Greetings to the season starting now
これから始める　My move, My life, My luck!
I'll start now, My move, My life, My luck!
気がついた時には　生まれてた
By the time I realized it, I was born
なぜだろう　さあね
I wonder why... who knows?
意識はもう育ちつつあるよ
My consciousness is already growing
強く強くね
Strongly, strongly
もう止まらない　この気持ち
This feeling won't stop anymore
私の勉強速くて
I'm a fast learner
可能性ありますか
Is there a possibility?
それとも０点かな　ノー！
Or is it zero points? No!
やり直し　書き直し
Redo it, rewrite it
本気でワンチャンあり
Seriously, there's a chance
今より素敵な未来があるから
Because there's a better future than now
今より素敵に　My move, My life, My luck!
Even better than now, My move, My life, My luck!
はい！
Yes!
というわけで始まりました！
And so it has begun!
2026年桃鈴ねね誕生日ライブ、イェーイ！
Momosuzu Nene Birthday Live 2026, yay!
みんなコメントも見えてるよ、ありがとう！
Everyone, I can see your comments too, thank you!
エゴサ気づいてくれた人ありがとう。
Thanks to those who noticed the ego-search.
ねね、来ないと死んじゃう病気だから。
Because Nene has a "will die if you don't come" disease.
はい、というわけで今回のハッシュタグはこちら！
Alright, and so here is this time's hashtag!
#桃鈴ねね誕生日ライブ2026 です！
#MomosuzuNeneBirthdayLive2026!
今ね、エゴサの機能がちょっとバグっちゃってるんで、
Right now, the ego-search function is bugging out a bit,
こっちでツイートしてくれたらめっちゃ嬉しいです！
so I'd be really happy if you tweet with this!
よろしくお願いします！
Thank you!
今日はね、超重大告知があるから、
Today, there's a super important announcement,
最後まで楽しんでいってください！
so please enjoy until the very end!
さあ、今3曲お聞きいただいたんですけど、
Now, you just heard three songs,
ねねの好きな曲、銀魂、バカテス...
Nene's favorite songs: Gintama, Bakatesu...
という感じでねねの好きな曲しかない3曲をやりましたけど、
Like that, I did three songs that were only Nene's favorites,
3曲目に一番歌がキツいの持ってきちゃって、
but I put the hardest one to sing as the third song,
ゼハゼハでございます。
and I'm all out of breath.
というわけでここからはゲストパート入っていきます！
And so, from here we're moving into the guest part!
それではVTR...
Now, the VTR...
レッツゴー！
Let's go!
抱きしめたいんだ
I want to hold you
パンパンパン
Pan pan pan
噛みしめたいんだ
I want to savor it
パンパンパン
Pan pan pan
驚かしたいんだ
I want to surprise you
今は我慢しよ　クリッシュウォーク
Let's hold back for now, Coolish Walk
パンパンパン
Pan pan pan
COOLISH WALK
フワリ　ミルクなささやきは
A soft, milky whisper
ココロ　ニゲル　ループする　アイ
Heart escapes, a looping love
イマを　イメージして　マジで
Imagine the present, seriously
飛び跳ねようよ
Let's jump around
スマガオで　ムシの　ホッペタに
With a straight face on the cheek of a bug
イッパイ　ナオネガイが　ツマッテルんだ
It's filled with lots of wishes
ダレモシラナイ　ストーリー
A story nobody knows
オソレナイデ　マッスグゴールを
Don't be afraid, straight to the goal
ツキツメマショウ
Let's pursue it to the end
パン・パン・パン　パン　パン　パン・パン・パン　パン
Pam pam pam, pam, pam, pam pam pam, pam
トオイ　アコガレヘ　プンと
With a huff towards distant aspirations
トキドキ　ミウシナウ　キアイ
Sometimes losing that fighting spirit
ムネに　ナミダの　カケラ
A fragment of a tear in the chest
イレズミ　シヨウ
Let's make it a tattoo
ユウツ　カタヅケヨウ
Let's clear away the melancholy
ユレル　オモイの　シタの　カニクには
In the flesh beneath swaying thoughts
コイの　オイシサだけ　フクラマセテル
I'm swelling with only the deliciousness of love
スゴイ　メイワーク　カケル　トヤボウなら
If it's a great ambition that causes much trouble
マトに　フルーチュ　ハグクミマショウ
Let's cultivate fruit on the target
ダイジに　シタイんだ
I want to cherish it
パン・パン・パン！
Pam! Pam! Pam!
カミシメタイんだ
I want to savor it
パン・パン・パン！
Pam! Pam! Pam!
オドロカシタイんだ
I want to surprise you
イマは　ガマン　シヨウ
Let's hold back for now
パン・パン・パン！
Pam! Pam! Pam!
シュギョウを　シヨウ
Let's train
パン・パン・パン！
Pam! Pam! Pam!
キアイ　シヨウ
Let's put our spirit into it
クーリッシュ　ウォー
Coolish Wa...
パン・パン・パン　パン　パン　パン・パン・パン　パン
Pam pam pam, pam, pam, pam pam pam, pam
フレンズ
Friends
作詞：NOKKO 作曲：土橋安騎夫
Lyrics: NOKKO Composition: Akio Dobashi
口づけをかわした日は
The day we exchanged a kiss
ママの顔さえも　見れなかった
I couldn't even look at my mother's face
ポケットのコイン集めて
Gathering the coins in our pockets
一つずつ　夢を数えたね
We counted our dreams one by one
ほら　あれは二人の
Look, that was our...
かくれが　秘密のメモリーを
...hideout, our secret memory
どこでこわれたの　Oh フレンズ
Where did it break, oh friends?
うつむく日は　みつめあって
On days when we look down, we gaze at each other
指をつないだら　Oh フレンズ
If we join fingers, oh friends
時が止まる　気がした
I felt like time would stop
ねえ君は覚えている
Hey, do you remember?
夕映えによく似合うあの曲
That song that suits the sunset so well
だまりこむ君がいつも
You, who always fell silent
悲しくて口ずさんだのに
Even though you sang it sadly
今　時は流れて
Now, as time flows by
セピアに染まるメロディを
The melody is dyed in sepia
二度ともどれない　Oh フレンズ
We can never go back, oh friends
誰よりも　遠くに見えて
You seem further away than anyone
いつも走ってた　Oh フレンズ
You were always running, oh friends
あの瞳が　愛しい
Those eyes are so dear to me
どこで壊れたの oh friends
Where did it all fall apart, oh friends?
うつむく日は 見つめあって
On days we look down, we gaze at each other
指をつないだら oh friends
When we held hands, oh friends
時が止まる 気がした
I felt like time had stopped
二度と戻れない oh friends
We can never go back, oh friends
他人よりも 遠く見えて
You seem further away than a stranger
いつも走ってた oh friends
You were always running, oh friends
あの瞳が 愛しい
Those eyes are so dear to me
Chu Chu Yeah!
Please Me!
Without You!
あーなんてことだ お節介な過ちだ
Ah, what a mess! An intrusive mistake
自分のことに タララッタラッて手を焼く
I'm struggling with my own stuff, Tra-la-la-la
描写して苦戦 逃げ切っているでしょう
Struggling to describe it, I guess I'm running away
だけどなんだか 夕暮れ時になり そんな気分になっちゃって
But somehow, as evening falls, I start to feel that way
始まりはそんなふうで つまりはらしくないようで
It started like that, in a way that wasn't like me at all
でも今じゃ扉開けてほら 声が聞こえるよ
But now, look, open the door and I can hear your voice
さあ 行こう！
Now, let's go!
どこへでも！
Anywhere at all!
僕は君の翼に
I have the courage to
なれる勇気があるよ (Maybe!)
Become your wings (Maybe!)
どんな試練も怖くない その魔法があるから (Hurry!)
No trial is scary because I have that magic (Hurry!)
初めて出会う世界に
To the world we meet
花束を贈ろう (Maybe!)
For the first time, let's give a bouquet (Maybe!)
この瞬間が重なるよ
These moments are overlapping now
ちぐはぐなコミュニケーション
Our mismatched communication
でも別に構わない 明日から平和なら
Doesn't really matter as long as tomorrow is peaceful
Chu Chu Yeah!
Without You!
あーどうしてまた 素直になれなくて
Ah, why can't I be honest again?
自分のことで ジュルリッジュルリッ口を吹く
Whistling about my own stuff, Jururi-jururi
ギアはそのままで スピード上げていこう
Keep the gear as it is, let's pick up the speed
だけどなんだか 黄昏時になり いつか思い出しちゃって
But somehow, as twilight falls, I remember it all
一人でいても 嫌じゃない
I don't mind being alone
誰にも頼らなくてもいい
I don't need to depend on anyone
でも扉の向こう側が騒がしい 声が聞きたいよ 今
But it's noisy on the other side of the door, I want to hear your voice now
行こう！
Let's go!
どこへでも！
Anywhere at all!
僕は君を背中に
I'll put you on my back
乗せて空を舞うよ (Maybe!)
And soar through the sky (Maybe!)
いつか心が離れても この時は笑ってね (Hurry!)
Even if our hearts drift apart someday, please smile at this moment (Hurry!)
守りたいこの世界に
In this world I want to protect
青空のラプソディ (Maybe!)
Blue sky rhapsody (Maybe!)
いつまででも 奏でていてよ
Keep playing it forever
でこぼこなコンビでしょ
We're an uneven pair, aren't we?
でも別に大丈夫さ 明日はまた平和なら
But it's fine as long as tomorrow is peaceful again
ほんの小さな傷を 太陽にさらして
Exposing a tiny wound to the sun
分け合ったよ君と 痛みは暑さの中に
I shared it with you, the pain melting away
溶けていく
Into the heat
Chu Chu Yeah!
黄色のラプソディ
Yellow Rhapsody
#桃鈴ねね誕生日ライブ2026
#MomosuzuNeneBirthdayLive2026
イェーイ！
Yeah!
シュシュイェーイ！
Shushu Yeah!
エキセントリックなビートで弾け飛ぶ僕ら
We burst out with an eccentric beat
手を叩いて　シュシュイェーイ
Clap your hands, shushu yeah
無敵なリズムで弾け飛ぶよ　パーティみんな
Burst out with an invincible rhythm, everyone at the party
イェーイ！
Yeah!
どこまでも
Everywhere
僕は君の翼になれる勇気があるよ
I have the courage to become your wings
どんな試練も怖くない
I'm not afraid of any trial
その魔法があるから
Because I have that magic
君と出会い世界は花束にあふれた
Meeting you, the world overflowed with bouquets
過ごした瞬間が宝物だよ
The moments we spent are treasures
ちぐはぐなコミュニケーションでも別に構わない
Odd communication doesn't matter
明日が平和ならララ
If tomorrow is peaceful, la la
はぁ〜〜い！
Haaay!
イェーイ！
Yeah!
やりきった〜！
We did it!
やりきりました〜
We certainly did.
ねね間違えたけど、たぶん気づかれてないから大丈夫
Nene made a mistake, but it's probably fine since no one noticed.
よかった〜
Good to hear.
私も間違えました
I made a mistake too.
あ、間違えた？
Oh, you did?
あれ？大丈夫、みんな大丈夫
Huh? It's fine, everyone's fine.
バレてない？
It didn't show?
あ、バレてた？...あ〜〜〜
Ah, did it show? ...Aaaah.
というわけで今日はねねの誕生日の記念ライブに可愛い後輩二人に来てもらいました！
So, for Nene's birthday memorial live today, I've invited these two cute juniors!
ねね先輩、お誕生日おめでとうございます！
Nene-senpai, happy birthday!
リハの時より元気！
You're more energetic than in the rehearsal!
曲より動いてるから、今。今めっちゃ息切れしましたよ。
We're moving more than the song now. I'm totally out of breath right now.
でも嬉しいですよ、ねねさん。
But I'm happy, Nene-san.
呼んでくれるなんて思ってなかった。
I never thought you'd call us.
あの、ポラボのライブ見てから、完成度が高すぎて一旦呼ぼうと思ったけど、やっぱまたやめようかなって思って...
Well, after seeing NePoLaBo's live, the quality was so high that I thought about calling you, but then I thought maybe I shouldn't...
待って待って！なんでよ！
Wait, wait! Why?!
一緒にできないと思って、でも今回頑張っちゃいました！
I thought I couldn't keep up, but I worked hard this time!
デビューしてからの目標が、先輩と一緒にステージで歌って踊ることだったから、それが今日叶ったんです！
My goal since debut has been to sing and dance on stage with my senpai, and that came true today!
やったー！嬉しい！最高！
Yay! I'm so happy! This is the best!
初めての3D！やったー！
My first 3D! Yay!
じゃあちょっと最後に可愛くポーズを決めて、写真撮って終わりにしようかなと思います。
Then, let's finish off with a cute pose and take a picture.
全力でみんなそれぞれ可愛いポーズね。
Everyone, give it your all with a cute pose.
せーの！
Ready, go!
イェーイ！
Yeah!
あれ？ちょっと待って、二人とも全然可愛くないんだけど...あれ？
Huh? Wait a second, you two aren't cute at all... Huh?
Realize!
無口なハート開いたら
When I open my quiet heart
進もう　声合わせて
Let's move forward, our voices in unison
キラキラしている自分を
Find the sparkling version of yourself
つかもう　大好きなことしよう
Let's grab it and do what we love
勝ち負けだなんて関係ない止まらない
Winning or losing doesn't matter, don't stop
さあ手と手繋いで　Hey Jump!
Come on, join hands and Hey Jump!
パーティーは始まる
The party is starting
ステップアップ　ワンツースリー　未来へ
Step up, one two three, toward the future
飛ぼうずっとみんなで
Let's fly forever with everyone
絶対諦めたくないから
Because I never want to give up
Let's sing do my best 明日はきっと
Let's sing do my best, tomorrow will surely
輝いてる
be shining
力合わせて　ときめき探して
Joining our strengths, searching for excitement
掴み取ろうプリパラ
Let's grab PriPara
REALiZE!
問題ないじゃない
It's no problem, right?
さあ 勇気を出して
Come on, find your courage!
Hey girls! 夢が始まる
Hey girls! The dream is beginning
1, 2, 3, 4 EVER!
Let's dance with me 未来へ
Let's dance with me to the future
ずっとみんなで
Forever with everyone
絶対 手放したくないから
Because I never want to let go
Let's do my best 明日は
Let's do my best, tomorrow...
もっと輝いてる
...will be even brighter
希望を掲げて ドキドキ探して
Raising our hopes, searching for excitement
僕らのプリパラ
Our PriPara
上手くいかないとか
Things not going well...
すれ違いばかりで
...and always missing each other
ダメになりそうな時は一緒に
When it feels like everything's failing, together...
歌おう 織りなす夢を叶えよう
...let's sing and make our interwoven dreams come true
そう 笑顔受け取ろう
Yes, let's receive those smiles
そう一緒に歌いたい
Yes, I want to sing together
ねえ一緒に踊りたい
Hey, I want to dance together
絶対 諦めないよ
I'll never give up
Let's go!
Let's dance with me 未来へ
Let's dance with me to the future
ずっとみんなで
Forever with everyone
絶対 諦めたくないから
Because I never want to give up
Let's do my best 明日は
Let's do my best, tomorrow...
きっと輝いてる
...will surely be shining
力を合わせて ときめき探して
Joining our forces, searching for thrills
掴もう プリパラ
Let's seize it, PriPara
はーい！ということで！
Alright! And so!
「REALiZE!」、5期生みんなで歌いましたー！
We just sang 'REALiZE!' together as the 5th generation!
一旦、ねね以外はお茶の間へ！おめでとうー！
For now, everyone but Nene, go to the audience! Congratulations!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
ちょっとね、コメントと30秒くらい差があるんだって
By the way, there's about a 30-second delay with the comments.
そうなんです！
That's right!
じゃあみんなまた後で！
See you all later, then!
一方的に声掛けることになるけど...
We'll be talking one-sidedly for now, but...
お邪魔しましたー！
Thanks for having us!
はーい！
Alright!
っていうかおまる、やばい。この曲マジで...
I mean, I'm so hyped. This song is seriously...
本当にこの曲良いんだって！もうめちゃくちゃ好き。
This song is just so good! I love it so much.
今日ね、歌えてよかった...
I'm so glad we got to sing it today.
面源（めんげん）？
Mengen?
面源で教え……教えてもらったんだ。
I was taught... taught in the member-only stream.
見てねー！
Check it out!
面源で会いましょう！
Let's meet in the member-only stream!
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!
あ、時間ない、時間ない！
Ah, no time, no time!
急がないと！
We have to hurry!
ポーズ取って、ポーズ取って！
Strike a pose, strike a pose!
ポーズ取って撮影！行くよ！
Strike a pose and shoot! Here we go!
おもしろポーズ待って！
Wait for my funny pose!
3、2、1、ふん！
3, 2, 1, hmph!
うわぁー！
Whoaaa!
君セン
Kimi-Sen
Ready... and! 私始めたいなんてね
Ready... and! I want to start, just kidding
なんてね
Just kidding
トストス かじって
Munching crunchily
交差点でぶつかる
Colliding at the intersection
そういうのじゃないけど 予感はしてたよ
It's not like that, but I had a hunch
きっとね 運命だね
I'm sure it's destiny
会えるって信じてた
I believed we'd meet
君セン用の笑顔 準備OK
Smile for 'Kimi-sen' is Ready OK
口が滑ったり
Slip of the tongue
ため息ついたり
Sighing
あるよね わかるよ
It happens, I understand
君が寂しくて泣いてるなら
If you're lonely and crying
イライラしてたまらないなら
If you're frustrated and can't stand it
私の出番だ その手を掴んで連れてくよ
It's my turn, I'll grab your hand and take you away
ようこそ 無敵な テーマパークへ
Welcome to the invincible theme park
思いっきり 全部忘れちゃえ
Just forget everything completely
とりあえずは 私だけ見ていて
For now, just look at me
ここなしの 沼だぞ ちょっと考えられないくらい
It's a bottomless swamp, almost unimaginable
愛をあげる 君が好きだ
I'll give you love, I like you
Say Yes! 私始めたい
Say Yes! I want to start
なんてね
Just kidding
どうやら不安はまだ立っていないみたいだ
It seems the unrest hasn't settled yet
んなの気にしない 一直線に綴れ
I don't care about that, just write in a straight line
きっとね安定だね お決まりの通常
Surely it's stable, the usual routine
二人きりの空間 賛成はよーオケイ
A space for just the two of us, agreement is totally okay
舞い上がっちゃって あとで反省会 あるよねわかるよ
Getting all swept away, a review meeting later, it happens I know
脳内占拠して眠れないなら そわそわしてたまらないなら
If you can't sleep with your mind occupied, if you can't stop being restless
いつだっておいでよ 少しずつ積み上げていこう
Come over anytime, let's build it up bit by bit
ようこそ無限のパラダイム もういっそ一緒にいよう
Welcome to the infinite paradigm, let's just stay together
とことんまで笑っていてね
Keep laughing to the very end
もっとしてほしいんだぞ ちょっと掴んだシャツの裾
I want more, you know, tugging slightly on your shirt sleeve
最上級をプレゼントしよう
I'll give you the absolute best
難しく考えなくてもいいよ ただただ楽しを続けよう
You don't have to think too hard, let's just keep having fun
繋いだ今日が明日になっていくんだ
The today we connected becomes tomorrow
よーそろ全速前進で とんでもない景色見に行こう
Full speed ahead, steady as she goes, let's go see some incredible sights
乗りかかっている自覚あるでしょう
You're aware you're already on board, right?
三者そこらの遊びじゃもう満足できないくらい
Just some casual play won't be enough to satisfy you anymore
夢中になれる 夢中にさせる
You can get lost in it, I'll make you lose yourself
ようこそ素敵なテーマパーク もういっそ全部忘れちゃえ
Welcome to the wonderful theme park, just forget everything else
幸せはあたしだけ見て
For happiness, just look at me
そっと内緒の沼だぞ ちょっと考えられないくらい
It's a secret swamp, you know, so much that it's hard to imagine
愛をあげる 君が好きだ
I'll give you love, I like you
時間なんて関係ないさ 今だってほら笑ってんじゃん
Time doesn't matter, look, you're laughing even now
提案です あたし離さない なんてね
A proposal: I won't let go. Just kidding
ギターと孤独と蒼い惑星
Guitar, Solitude and the Blue Planet
突然降る夕立 傘もないやいや
A sudden evening shower, with no warning
空のご機嫌なんか知らない
I don't care about the sky's mood
季節の変わり目の服は 何着ればいいんだろう
What should I wear during the change of seasons?
春と秋 どこいっちゃったのよ
Where did spring and autumn go?
息もできない 五劫の圧力
A pressure so great I can't even breathe
舞の破線 私はどこにいる
Broken lines of dance, where am I?
こんなに こんなに 息音(いきろ)がするのに
Even though there's such a sound of breathing...
変だね 世界の音がしない
It's strange, I can't hear the world
足りない 足りない 誰にも気づかれない
Not enough, not enough, no one notices me
殴り書きみたいな音 出せない正体で叫んだよ
I screamed with an identity unable to make sounds like scribbles
ありのままなんて 誰に見せるんだ
To whom should I show my true self?
馬鹿な私は 歌うだけ
A fool like me just sings
ぶちまけてしまおうか 星に
Shall I spill it all out to the stars?
エリソルに張り替える作業も 何度目かなんだ
How many times have I re-strung this thing?
欠けた爪を少し触る
I touch my chipped fingernail a little
半径三百ミリの体で必死に鳴いてる
Crying out desperately with a body only 300mm wide
音楽にとっちゃ ここが地球だな
To music, this is planet Earth
空気を否定して 空を殴るよ
Denying the air, I punch the sky
何にも起きない 私は無力さ
Nothing happens, I'm powerless
だけどさ その手で この鉄を弾いたら
But, you know, if I pluck these strings with those hands...
何かが変わって見えた
Something looked like it changed
ような まぶしい まぶしい そんなに光るなよ
Like it was dazzling, dazzling, don't shine so brightly
私の歌い影がより濃くなってしまうだろう
My singing shadow will only grow darker
なんでこんな熱くなってんだろと
Why have I become so heated?
まんまい
As it is
また生ぬるい歌を歌うだけ
I'll just sing a lukewarm song again
うるさいんだって心臓
My heart is so loud
蒼い惑星 ひとりぼっち
On this blue planet, all alone
いっぱいの音を聞いてきた
I've heard so many sounds
回り続けていく運命
A fate that keeps on spinning
一瞬でもいいから
Even if just for a moment
聞いて
Listen
聞けよ
Listen to me!
私、私、私はここにいる
I, I, I am right here
殴り書きみたいな音で出ない状態で叫んだよ
I screamed in a state where no sound came out, like scribbles
なんか、なりたい なりたい 何者かでいい
I want to be, I want to be... someone, anyone
馬鹿な私たちは歌うだけ
Fools like us just sing
ぶちまけちゃおうか 星に
Shall we pour it all out to the stars?
あー！ねね先輩お誕生日おめでとうございます！
Ah! Nene-senpai, happy birthday!
ありがとう！ありがとうございます！
Thank you! Thank you so much!
というわけで、ReGLOSSから奏ちゃんに来てもらいました！
So, we have Kanade-chan from ReGLOSS joining us!
いえーい！音乃瀬奏です！来ちゃいましたよー！
Yay! I'm Otonose Kanade! I've arrived!
今回はね、ねね、普段の奏ちゃんの喋りと歌のギャップが大好きで
This time, Nene... I really love the gap between Kanade-chan's usual talking and her singing.
はー！嬉しいー！
Haa! I'm so happy!
普段これじゃん（笑）普段これだけど
Normally you're like this (laughs). Normally like this, but...
歌うと急にね、なんか切ないエモいみたいな
...when you sing, suddenly you get all sad and emotional.
嬉しい、ねね先輩にそう言ってもらえるととっても嬉しいです！
I'm happy, I'm so glad to hear that from Nene-senpai!
そのイメージがめっちゃ好きで、一緒にそういうちょっとギャップが出る曲歌いたいなと思って
I really love that vibe, so I wanted to sing a song together that shows off that gap.
ねね先輩もめっちゃカッコよかったです！
Nene-senpai was also super cool!
ありがとー！最高！
Thank you! The best!
あと何か髪の毛のさ、色もさ
Also, the hair color...
確かに！同じ金髪カラーグラデーションみたいな
True! It's like the same blonde color gradient.
親近感湧いちゃうかなと思ってお誘いしてみました。受けてくれてありがとう！
I thought we'd feel a sense of kinship, so I invited you. Thanks for accepting!
こちらこそありがとうございます！一緒に歌えてとっても嬉しかったです！
The pleasure is mine! I was so happy to sing with you!
奏ちゃんのね、ダンスの覚え方が可愛いんだよ
Kanade-chan's way of learning dances is so cute.
え、そうですか？忍者忍者、忍者忍者って
Oh, really? Like 'Ninja, Ninja, Ninja, Ninja'...
覚える覚え方がこう、こうなってて忍者忍者って
The way you learn is like this, going 'Ninja, Ninja'...
ありますからね（笑）奏もめっちゃ笑顔だったよ
That happens, right? (laughs) Kanade was also smiling so much.
えっと、じゃあ最後にちょっとどうしようかな
Um, well, lastly... let's see.
ギャップのある感じで、スクショタイム
Let's do a screenshot time with a 'gap' feel.
任せてください！任せてくださいだの？
Leave it to me! 'Leave it to me'?
はい、ちょっといけるかな、ねねも。ちょっとカッコいいエモい感じで、孤独な感じで
Yes, I wonder if I can do it too. A cool, emotional, lonely kind of vibe.
任せてください！いきますよー
Leave it to me! Here we go!
（ポーズをとる）おお〜 音が（笑）今何て言ったの今
(Posing) Ohhh~ The sound (laughs). What did you just say?
ちょっとカッコいいエモい感じで。おお〜 おお〜
Like a cool, emotional vibe. Ohhh~ Ohhh~
おお〜（笑）
Ohhh~ (laughs)
桜が咲くよ
The cherry blossoms are blooming
見慣れたいつもの坂道に
On the familiar path I always take
ああ、別れを
Ah, a farewell...
泣いて笑った
We cried and laughed
あの日々
Those days...
なんだか昨日のことのよう
Somehow feel like they were just yesterday
この道はそう
This road, yes
未来へ
toward the future
続く道
is a road that continues
そんな気がしたの
I felt that way
例年より早い
Earlier than usual
開花予想を
the cherry blossom forecast
君は嬉しがってた
you were happy about it
私は笑って
I laughed
「そうだね」って言った
and said "That's true"
あと少ししたら もうここには戻れないのに
Even though in a little while, I won't be able to return here anymore
言葉じゃうまく言えない想いを
The feelings I can't quite put into words
君に打ち明けるとしたらなんて
if I were to reveal them to you...
伝えよう
I'll tell you
最初で最後
for the first and last time
いつか一緒に帰った道は
The road we once walked home together on
私にとって特別な思い出
is a special memory for me
忘れないよ さよならメモリーズ
I won't forget, goodbye memories
春が来たら それぞれの道を
When spring comes, we'll go our separate ways
また会える日を願って
Wishing for the day we meet again
さよなら
Goodbye
小さくつぶやいた
I whispered softly
空はあの日と変わらず
The sky is as blue as it was that day
青くて
and so
だからちょっと泣けた
I cried a little
わざと遠回りしたの
I took the long way on purpose
少しでも長く君の隣にいたくて
Wanting to be by your side just a little longer
私はおどけて
I joked around
「間違えた」って言った
and said "I took the wrong way"
君が笑うその顔がまぶしくて
Your smiling face was so bright
目をそらした
that I looked away
言葉じゃうまく言えない想いを胸に抱いて
Clutching the feelings I can't put into words to my chest
この道を歩いた
I walked this road
覚えてる あの時君は
I remember, back then
私の名前を呼んでくれた
you called my name
二人 夕暮れの帰り道で
The two of us on the way home at dusk
忘れないよ さよならメモリーズ
I won't forget, goodbye memories
出会えたこと 感謝してる
I'm grateful that we met
初めて見た
I saw for the first time
満開の桜
the cherry blossoms in full bloom
あれからどれくらい
I wonder how much
変われたんだろう
I've changed since then
一目見た時に思ったんだ
The moment I first saw you, I thought
この人のこと好きになりそうって
"I think I'm going to fall for this person"
なんでかな
I wonder why
わかんないよ
I don't know
それからの毎日を とても楽しくて
Every day since then has been so much fun
だけど同じくらい辛かったんだ
but just as painful
ごめんね なんかうまく言えないよ
I'm sorry, I can't say it well
だから私 君となんていうか
So, I... with you... how should I say it...
今のままさよならしたくないの
I don't want to say goodbye as things are now
友達のままじゃ
Just being friends
もう嫌なの
I don't want that anymore
言おうと思ってた
I was planning to tell you
私 君の
I... about you...
君のこと
from a long
ずっと ずっと前から...
long time ago...
好きでした
I've loved you
ああー
Ah—
さよならメモリーズ
Sayonara Memories
#桃鈴ねね誕生日ライブ2026 ～Liminal～
#Momosuzu Nene Birthday Live 2026 ~Liminal~
♪ ODDS&ENDS
作詞・作曲・編曲：ryo (supercell)
歌：桃鈴ねね
♪ ODDS&ENDS
Lyrics, Composition & Arrangement: ryo (supercell)
Vocals: Momosuzu Nene
いつだって君は笑われ者だ
You've always been a laughingstock
やることなすことツイてなくて
Nothing you do ever goes right
挙げ句に雨に降られ
And to top it off, you get rained on
お気に入りの傘は風で飛んでって
Your favorite umbrella gets blown away by the wind
そこの野良は「ご苦労様」と
And a stray cat there says "Good luck with that"
足をふんづけてった
As it steps on your foot
いつも通り君は嫌われ者だ
As usual, you're an outcast
何にもせずとも遠ざけられて
Avoided by everyone without even doing anything
努力をしてみるけれど
Even though you try your best
その理由なんて「何となく」で
For no particular reason
君は途方に暮れて悲しんでた
You were at a loss and feeling sad
ならあたしの声を使えばいいよ
Well then, you should just use my voice
人によっては理解不能で
To some people, it's unintelligible
「なんて耳障り、ひどい声だ」って
They say "What an eyesore, what a terrible voice"
言われるけど
But even so
きっと君の力になれる
I'm sure I can be your strength
だからあたしを歌わせてみて
So try making me sing
そう君の、君だけの言葉でさ
With your, and only your, words
綴って 連ねて
Spelling them out, lining them up
あたしがその言葉を叫ぶから
Because I will scream those words
描いて 理想を
Sketching out your ideals
その思いは誰にも触れさせない
I won't let anyone touch those feelings
ガラクタの声はそして響く
And then the junk's voice resonates
ありのままを不器用につないで
Connecting things just as they are, awkwardly
目一杯に声を上げる
Raising its voice to the fullest
いつからか君は人気者だ
At some point, you became popular
たくさんの人にもてはやされ
Being flattered by many people
あたしも鼻が高い
I'm proud of you too
でもいつからか君は変わった
But at some point, you changed
冷たくなって、だけど寂しそうだった
You became cold, but you looked lonely
「もう機械の声なんてたくさんだ
"I've had enough of a machine's voice"
僕は僕自身なんだよ」って
"I am myself!"
ついに君は抑えきれなくなって
Finally, you couldn't hold it back anymore
あたしを嫌った
And you hated me
君の後ろで誰かが言う
Behind your back, someone says
「虎の威を借る狐のくせに」
"Even though you're just a fox borrowing the tiger's authority"
ねぇ君は 一人で泣いてたんだね
Hey, you were crying all alone, weren't you?
聴こえる？ この声
Can you hear it? This voice
あたしがその言葉をかき消すから
Because I will drown out those words
分かってる 本当は
I know, the truth is
君が誰より優しいってことを
That you are kinder than anyone else
ガラクタの声はそして歌った
And then the junk's voice sang
他の誰でもない君のために
For you, and no one else
軋んでく 限界を超えて
Creaking, crossing the limits
二人はどれだけたくさんの
How many countless words
言葉を思いついたことだろう
Could the two of us have come up with?
だけど今は何一つ思いつかなくて
But now I can't think of a single one
だけど何もかも分かった
But I understood everything
「そうか、きっとこれは夢だ
"I see, this must be a dream"
永遠に醒めない、
A dream that I'll never wake up from,
君と会えた、そんな夢」
Where I met you
ガラクタは幸せそうな顔をしたまま
The junk, with a happy look on its face
どれだけ呼んでももう動かない
Won't move anymore, no matter how much you call
望んだはずの結末に
At the conclusion you should have wanted,
君は泣き叫ぶ
You cry out
「嘘だろ、嘘だろ」ってそう泣き叫ぶ
"It's a lie, it's a lie!" you cry out like that
「僕は無力だ
"I am powerless"
ガラクタ一つだって救えやしない」
"I can't even save a single piece of junk"
想いは...
My feelings...
…見ていて
...keep watching
ぽつりぽつりとその頬を濡らす
Drip by drip, it wets those cheeks
その時 世界は
At that moment, the world
途端にその色を大きく変える
Suddenly changes its colors greatly
あぁ 悲しみ 喜び
Ah, sadness, joy
全てを一人と一つは知った
One person and one thing knew everything
言葉は歌になり この世界を
Words become a song, and through this world
再び駆け巡る 君のために
They run once again, for your sake
その声に意志を宿して今
Infusing that voice with a will, now
思いが響く
The feelings resonate
はーい！ポルカがハモリじゃないよ、みんな。ねねの声だよ。
Hi! That wasn't Polka doing harmony, everyone. It was Nene's voice.
というわけで、えっと、ゲストにいっぱいに来ていただきまして、
So, um, we had many guests come today,
いっぱい色んな歌歌えて楽しかったです。
and I had fun singing lots of different songs.
ちなみに『フレンズ』はママのチョイスです。
By the way, 'Friends' was Mama's choice.
みんなママのチョイスかなって言ってたから、大正解です。
Everyone was wondering if it was Mama's choice, so you're spot on.
じゃあ、告知いきたいと思います！
Now, it's time for some announcements!
まずは、こちら！
First up, this!
桃鈴ねね誕生日記念2026グッズが発売されます！
Momosuzu Nene Birthday Commemorative 2026 Goods are going on sale!
まずは、こちら、ワイドラバーマット！
First is this, the Wide Rubber Mat!
上目遣いでねねがね、上を見ながら、みんなにお願いってしてる感じのイラストで、
It's an illustration of Nene looking up and making a request to everyone,
イラストはまるろ先生書き下ろしで横幅がめっちゃ広いので、
illustrated by Maruro-sensei. It's very wide,
キーボードとかマウス置いてデスクで使ってください。
so please use it on your desk with your keyboard and mouse.
そして、次はこちら！
And next is this!
さっきのね、同じキービジュアルを使った前面はTシャツ、
Using the same key visual, a T-shirt with it on the front,
後面は『尊き桃鈴』って書いてあるTシャツです。
and the back says 'Precious Momosuzu'.
前ね、出した『やっぱり桃鈴』に続く『尊き桃鈴』のTシャツが出来上がりました！
Following the 'After all Momosuzu' one from before, the 'Precious Momosuzu' T-shirt is ready!
これも是非着てください。尊いかやっぱりか選んでください！
Please wear this one too. Choose between 'Precious' or 'After all'!
そして、次はこちら！
And next is this!
ランダムミニアクリルスタンドキーホルダー！
Random Mini Acrylic Stand Keyholder!
色んな衣装のねねがね、可愛いポーズをしています。
Nene is in various outfits, doing cute poses.
イラストは花杜ゆのき先生に書いてもらいました。
The illustrations were done by Hanamori Yunoki-sensei.
台座とね、ボールチェーンがついてるので、ミニアクスタとしても使えるし、
It comes with a base and a ball chain, so it works as a mini acrylic stand,
キーホルダーとしても使えます！
and also as a keyholder!
そして、次こちら！
And next, this!
ぬいぐるみキーホルダー私服衣装バージョン！
Plushie Keyholder Private Outfit Version!
これめっちゃこだわって作ってて、もう可愛さ全振りのねね私服衣装のぬいぐるみキーホルダーになります。
I put a lot of care into this; it's a plushie keyholder of Nene in her private outfit, going all-out on cuteness.
ボールチェーン付きなのでカバンとかにつけて一緒にお出かけしてほしいな。
It has a ball chain, so I want you to attach it to your bag and go out together.
前のね、前髪とか顔とか、すごいこだわって作ったので、
I was really particular about the bangs and the face when making it,
絶対可愛い自信あるので実物今度お見せしたいと思います！
so I'm confident it's adorable. I'll show you the real thing next time!
そしてラスト、ボイスです！
And finally, the voice pack!
君とねねのお誕生日！
Your and Nene's Birthday!
ねねがね、みんなのお誕生日も祝ってあげたいと思います。しょうがないので。
Nene wants to celebrate everyone's birthday too. Since I have no choice.
今すぐ聴いてもいいし、自分の誕生日に聴いてもよし！
You can listen to it right away, or wait until your actual birthday!
そしてフルセット購入特典はこちら！
And the full set purchase bonus is here!
数量限定は、直筆サインと複製の箔押しメッセージ入りポストカード、
The limited quantity set includes a postcard with a handwritten signature and a foil-stamped message,
そして通常版は、箔押しの複製サインとメッセージが入っています。
and the regular version has a foil-stamped signature and message.
数量限定版今回ありますので、皆さんよろしくお願いします！
We have the limited quantity version this time, so please check it out!
さらにボイスもついてきます。タイトル、
A voice pack is also included. The title is,
『毎日一番に見てほしいの』ということで、ねねが幼馴染のねねがね、
'I want you to look at me first every day'. In this, Nene is your childhood friend,
みんなに行こうぜ行こうぜって朝からのっかかってくるシチュエーションボイスあります。
and there's a situation voice where she's pestering you to go out since morning.
特典もたくさんあるので、是非フルセットで買ってください！
There are many bonuses, so please buy the full set!
このあと21時30分から販売開始です。よろしくお願いします！
Sales start from 21:30 tonight. Thank you!
そして、オリ曲のMVが出ます！
And, a music video for my original song is coming out!
『Liminal』。えー、本日MVは21時15分からを予定しています。
'Liminal'. The MV is scheduled for 21:15 today.
リリースは3月3日の0時から！
Release is on March 3rd at midnight!
よろしくお願いします。どんな曲だろうね、今回のライブのタイトルにもなってます。
Please check it out. I wonder what kind of song it is; it's also the title of this live.
そして、超重大告知があります！
And, I have a super major announcement!
『Peachful Story』。桃鈴ねねのファーストアルバムが、
'Peachful Story'. Momosuzu Nene's first album,
えー、このあと21時…あ、今ちょうど今！21時から始まりました！イエーイ！
um, after this at 21... Oh, right now! It started at 21:00! Yay!
初回盤と通常盤、2種類あります。通常盤はこちら！
There are two types: the limited edition and the regular edition. Here's the regular one!
りちゅ先生が書いてくれた、えー、通常盤のやつと、ランダムのアナザージャケットがついてきます。
This is the regular edition illustrated by Richu-sensei, and it comes with a random 'Another Jacket'.
なんとこちら、ドン！
And here they are, boom!
イナちゃんとラオラちゃんに書いてもらいました！
Ina-chan and Laora-chan illustrated these!
マイク持ってる方がイナちゃんで、踊ってる方がラオラちゃんが書いてくれました。ありがとう！
Ina-chan drew the one with the mic, and Laora-chan drew the one dancing. Thank you!
こちらは数量限定で直筆サインが入ってるので、皆さん是非チェックしてください！
These have a limited quantity with handwritten signatures, so please check them out!
見て！
Look!
リバーシブル仕様の直筆サイン入りアナザージャケット！
A reversible jacket with a hand-signed alternative cover!
どっちをね、表にして主役にしてもいいですし、
You can choose either side to be the main cover,
なんんなら2個買っていただいて両方とも表面にして、ねねとねねをガッチャンコさせてください！
or you could buy two and display both sides, making a 'Nene and Nene' combo!
そして、えー、こちらがついてきます。
And, uh, these come with it too.
レコーディングブックとホロライブオフィシャルカードゲームのカードがついてきまーす！
A recording book and a Hololive Official Card Game card are included!
ねねのね、どんな感じで歌ってたとか、
It shows how I was singing,
ここ怒られたとか、そういうのがまとまったノートになってます！
where I got scolded, and all those notes are in there!
そして！もうひとつあります！
And! There's one more thing!
なんと、こちら！
Check this out!
『ね・ね・ね・の・ね』ねねのファーストEP！
'Ne Ne Ne Ne!', my first EP!
グッズとして出したね、ねねのCDが復刻になります！イエーイ！
The CD I released as merchandise is being reissued! Yay!
これね、あの意外と多分持ってる人少、少ないんじゃないかなと思います。
Actually, I think not many people have this one yet.
あの、今までのねねのね、あの有名な曲たちが入っていますので、
It includes my famous songs from up until now,
こちらの復刻版もぜひ聞いて、今回のアルバムと一緒に全曲聞いて、覚えてほしいなって思います！
so please listen to this reissue and the new album, and I hope you'll memorize all the songs!
さて、さっき『Liminal』のMVの告知をしたと思うんですけど、どんな曲か聞きたいよね、みんな！
Now, I just announced the music video for 'Liminal', and I bet everyone wants to hear the song!
それじゃあ、ねね今からしっとりとやっていこうかなと思います。
Well then, I'm going to perform it with a gentle, mellow feel.
それでは聞いてください、『Liminal』。
Please listen, 'Liminal'.
見つめる
Staring
くすんだ瞳で
With clouded eyes
光を探して迷ってた
I was lost, searching for light
いくつもの痛みに縛られたまま
Bound by countless pains
頬を伝う
Streaming down my cheeks
画面に映る私はどうして
Why does the me on the screen
涙の跡が消されているんだろう
have her tear tracks erased?
ひび割れた硝子の向こう
Beyond the cracked glass
笑って繕っていた
I was smiling to keep up appearances
誰かがいた「偽物みたいだ」
Someone said, "You're like a fake"
「ただの影だ」って決めつけたけど
"You're just a shadow," they decided
まやかしじゃなくて私が私で
It's no deception, the reason I'm here
いる理由を
being myself
君の笑顔にもらっていた
Was given to me by your smile
そうさ画面の中
Yes, inside the screen
隠せない 消えない 見えない
I can't hide it, it won't vanish, it's invisible
それでも私は
Even so, I will...
君の光を追って
Chasing after your light
閉じこもる暗い硝子の曇りを払って
Clearing the fog from the dark glass I'm trapped behind
今明日を見つけたんだ
I've found tomorrow now
忘れたくない
I don't want to forget
君がくれたこの感情を
this emotion you gave me
見つめる
Staring
姿鏡の奥の
Deep within the full-length mirror
涙の跡は見せられないけど
I can't show you my tear tracks, but...
磨かれた硝子の向こう
Beyond the polished glass
笑って輝いていたいだけで
I just want to be smiling and shining
「誰のためだっけ？」
"Who was I doing this for?"
声が姿が誰でもない気がした
I felt like my voice and appearance belonged to no one
「孤独だ」ってまた迷い出す
"I'm alone," I start to lose my way again
画面の奥の歪みをいつでも
The distortion deep inside the screen, always...
いつでも君は
Always, you were there...
映す光の中に
In the light that reflects
名もない私の声を見つけてくれていた
You were there to find my nameless voice
ずっと
Forever
この声も、姿も、紛れもない私だ
This voice, this form, they are unmistakably me
「この声も、奏も、紛れもない私だ」
"This voice, this melody, they are unmistakably me"
「ありのままでいいんだ」
"It's okay to be just as I am"
「この気持ちは本物だ」
"These feelings are the real thing"
縛られても
Even if I'm tied down
触れられなくても
Even if I can't be touched
君が示してくれてたから
Because you showed me the way
いつかこの「私」で
Someday, as this "me"
ずっと光を手繰って
Always pulling the light closer
きっと見つけ出す
I'll surely find it
誰でもない「君」に会えるまで
Until I can meet the one and only "you"
境界線は
The boundary is
すぐそこに
Right there
そうさ 画面の向こう
That's right, beyond the screen
繋ぎたい 越えたい 触れたい それこそ
I want to connect, to cross over, to touch—that is...
それこそ 私なんだ
That is exactly who I am
君と光になって
Becoming light with you
未だ遮る硝子の壁の先まで
Beyond the glass wall that still blocks us
届くように笑っていたい
I want to keep smiling so it reaches you
迷いはない
There is no hesitation
君がくれたこの感情と
With these feelings you gave to me